<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.10.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-02-21T15:19:30-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">magnus-opus.xyz</title><subtitle>THE CONSTITUTION IS FALLEN! LONG LIVE THE CONSTITUTION!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Magnus-Opus!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/update/2025/02/18/welcome-to-Magnus-Opus.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Magnus-Opus!" /><published>2025-02-18T19:45:14-08:00</published><updated>2025-02-18T19:45:14-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/update/2025/02/18/welcome-to-Magnus-Opus</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/update/2025/02/18/welcome-to-Magnus-Opus.html"><![CDATA[<p>THE CONSTITUTION IS FALLEN<br />
LONG LIVE THE CONSTITUTION</p>

<p>History tells us the proper process to carry out at this point in time. We simply repeat the process.</p>

<p>I ask all inhabitants of the United States and citizens abroad to contact their state level legislators (and governors, etc) and encourage them to meet in session and vote to approve a state declaration of independence from the puppet government of the Trump administration, and his sycophantic jurors and legislators, and initiate the process of instantiating a new Federal government of duly elected officials, appointees, cabinets, departments, etc, etc, etc…</p>

<p>For the States of California, Oregon, and Washington; I encourage you to <strong>lead the way</strong> by unifying in your vote to send such a declaration and to join in the Cascadian Coalition of Free States (working title, in lieu of <em>Nation McNationface</em>).</p>

<p>For an example of what such a declaration would look like, please see this proposed template for the new <a href="/docs/declaration">declaration</a>. READ THE NEW DECLARATION</p>

<p>For an overview of this project, please consider the <a href="/docs/declaration">declaration</a> and read the project <a href="/overview">overview</a>.</p>

<p>To help spread the word, contact your state legislature and tell them, THE CONSTITUTION IS FALLEN! LONG LIVE THE CONSTITUTION! That you are encouraging them to meet in session and vote to send a declaration of independence and to join with any other state or former US territory, commonwealth, or district; for the purpose of forming a new government under the US Constitution.</p>

<p><em>Coming soon:</em> Scripts, templates, and <strong>swag</strong>!</p>

<p>THE CONSTITUTION IS FALLEN<br />
LONG LIVE THE CONSTITUTION</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="update" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE CONSTITUTION IS FALLEN LONG LIVE THE CONSTITUTION]]></summary></entry></feed>